Framed, abandoned, but never defeated.
Behind Enemy Lines III: Colombia is a war, action,
thriller film directed by Tim Matheson.
Navy SEALS mount an attack on Colombian special forces to
clear their names and rescue a hostage.
Commander Scott Boytano, played by Keith David.
MCPO Carter Holt, played by Ken Anderson.
LT. Sean Macklin, played by Joe Manganiello.
Petty Officer 2nd Class Kevin Derricks, played by Channon Roe.
Alvaro Cardona, played by Yancey Arias.
Petty Officer 3rd Class Steve Gaines, played by Chris Johnson.
Behind Enemy Lines: Colombia is a 2009 American action war film directed by
Tim Matheson and starring Joe Manganiello, WWE wrestler Mr.
Kennedy, Keith David and Matheson.
It is the third installment in the Behind Enemy Lines film series, following
Behind Enemy Lines, and Behind Enemy Lines II: Axis of Evil.
The film was co-produced by WWE Studios, written by Tobias Iaconis
and released direct-to-video on January 6, 2009.
Keith David is the only cast member to have returned in this film.
The tone is intense.